Finding Aid for the Pinal Dome Oil Company Records LSC.0220
UCLA Library Special Collections
Pinal Dome Oil Company records
1893-1926
UCLA Library Special Collections
Pinal Dome Oil Company
LSC.0220
55.0 Linear Feet (110 boxes and 9 oversize boxes)
The Pinal Oil Company originated in Santa Maria, California, ca. 1901; the original nine directors, constituting the bulk of the stockholders, were: E.W. Clark, J.W. Atkinson (vice president), Marks Fleisher (president), Sam Fleisher, D.D. Barnard, C.E. Reed, A.H. McKay, Pat Moore, and James F. Goodwin (secretary). The company later merged with Dome Oil Company (ca. 1911) to form the Pinal Dome Oil Company and was bought by Union Oil ca. July 1917. The collection consists primarily of business correspondence and financial records but also contains blueprints and maps, inventories, journals, transcripts of lawsuits, and well drilling reports.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Guy L. Goodwin, 1942. Additions in March and April 1991.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID:9942335893606533
Biography
The Pinal Oil Company originated in Santa Maria, California, ca. 1901; the original nine directors, constituting the bulk of the stockholders, were: E.W. Clark, J.W. Atkinson (vice president), Marks Fleisher (president), Sam Fleisher, D.D. Barnard, C.E. Reed, A.H. McKay, Pat Moore, and James F. Goodwin (secretary). The company later merged with Dome Oil Company (ca. 1911) to form the Pinal Dome Oil Company and was bought by Union Oil ca. July 1917.
Scope and Content
The collection consists primarily of business correspondence and financial records but also contains blueprints and maps, inventories, journals, transcripts of lawsuits, and well drilling reports.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Blueprints and Maps (Includes blueprints and plans for buildings, gasoline storage facilities, and equipment and maps of Santa Maria Fields and other oil production sites)
Company History (Documents related to history of Pinal Dome Oil Company)
Correspondence (Comprised of business correspondence and personal correspondence between Pinal Oil, Dome Oil, and Pinal Dome Oil and their respective allies and subsidiaries)
Financial Records and Reports (Includes account books, ledgers, stock certificates, payrolls, and tax documents of Pinal Dome Oil Company and its subsidiaries)
Inventories and Tour Reports (Consists of driller's tour reports, well reports, and inventories of refineries and production)
Legal Documents (Abstracts of title, by-laws, articles of incorporation, and indentures belonging to Pinal Dome Oil Company and its allies and subsidiaries)
Related Material
Union Oil Company of California Records (Collection 449). Department of Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Petroleum industry and trade -- California -- Archives.; Pinal Dome Oil Company -- Correspondence
- Blueprints and Maps
  - undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - [undated], [oversized] (Box 85)
- Company History
  - undated, [1 of 4 folders.] (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - undated, [2 of 4 folders.] (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - undated, [3 of 4 folders.] (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - undated, [4 of 4 folders.] (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Correspondence
  - 1916 March 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1916 March 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1916 March 11-20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1916 March 11-20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1916 March 21-25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1916 March 25-31 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1916 March 21-31 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1916 September 21-30 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1916 September 21-30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1916 October 1-4 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1916 October 5-10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1916 October 11-14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1916 October 15-20 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1916 October 21-25 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1916 October 26-31 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1917 April 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1917 April 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1917 April 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1917 May 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1917 May 11-15 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1917 May 16-20 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1917 May 21-31 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1917 May 21-31 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1917 May 21-31 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1909 January-March (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1909 April-July (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1909 August-October (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1909 November-December (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1911 April (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1911 May (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1911 June 1-20 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1911 June 21-30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1911 July (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1912 January (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1912 February 1-20 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1912 February 21-March 10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1912 March 11-31 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1912 April 1-20 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1912 April 21-May 19 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1912 May 20-June 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1912 June 4-15 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1912 June 16-30 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1912 July 1-22 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1912 July 23-31 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1912 August 1-15 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1912 August 16-31 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1912 September 1-15 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1912 September 16-30 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1912 October 1-15 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1912 October 16-31 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1912 November 1-30 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1912 December 1-15 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1912 December 16-31 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1913 January 1-20 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1913 January 21-February 10 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1913 February 11-20 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1913 February 21-28 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1913 March 1-10 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1913 March 11-20 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1913 March 21-31 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1913 April 1-10 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1913 April 11-30 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1913 May 1-13 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1913 May 14-31 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1913 June 1-10 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1913 June 11-20 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1913 June 21-30 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1913 July 1-10 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1913 July 11-20 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1913 July 21-31 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1913 August 1-20 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1913 August 21-31 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1913 September 1-10 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1913 September 11-20 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1913 September 21-30 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1913 October 1-10 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1913 October 11-20 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1913 October 21-31 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1913 November 1-13 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 1913 November 14-30 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 1913 December 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 1913 December 11-20 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 1913 December 21-31 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 1914 January 1-20 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 1914 January 21-31 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 1914 February 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 1914 February 11-28 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 1914 March 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 1914 March 11-20 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 1914 March 21-31 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1914 April 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 1914 April 11-20 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 1914 April 21-30 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 1914 May 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 1914 May 11-20 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1914 May 21-31 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 1914 June 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 1914 June 11-20 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1914 June 21-31 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 1914 July 1-10 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1914 July 11-20 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 1914 July 21-31 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 1914 August 1-10 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1914 August 11-20 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1914 August 21-31 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 1914 September 1-10 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 1914 September 11-20 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 1914 September 21-30 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1914 October 1-6 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1914 October 6-10 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 1914 October 11-20 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 1914 October 21-31 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 1914 November 1-10 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 1914 November 11-20 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1914 November 21-30 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 1914 December 1-10 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1914 December 11-20 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1914 December 21-31 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 1915 January 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 1915 January 11-20 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 1915 January 21-31 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - 1915 February 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - 1915 February 11-20 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1915 February 21-28 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1915 March 1-10 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1915 March 11-20 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1915 March 21-31 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Oakland Station., 1915 January-May (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Oakland Station., 1915 June-September (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Oakland Station., 1915 October-December (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 1915 April 1-10 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1915 April 11-20 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 1915 April 21-30 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 1915 May 1-10 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 1915 May 11-20 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 1915 May 21-31 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 1915 June 1-5 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 1915 June 6-10 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 1915 June 11-13 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 1915 June 14-20 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 1915 June 21-30 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 1915 July 1-10 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 1915 July 11-20 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 1915 July 21-26 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 1915 July 27-31 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 1915 August 1-10 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - 1915 August 11-20 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 1916 June 1-10 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 1916 June 1-10 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1916 June 11-20 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 1916 June 11-20 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 1916 June 21-30 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 1916 June 21-30 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 1916 August 11-20 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 1916 August 11-20 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - 1916 August 21-31 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 1916 August 21-31 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - 1916 September 1-10 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 1916 September 11-14 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 1916 September 15-20 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 1917 July 1-10 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 1917 July 11-20 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 1917 July 11-20 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 1917 July 21-31 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 1917 August 1-10 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 1917 August 11-20 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 1917 August 21-31 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 1917 September 1-10 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - 1917 September 11-20 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - 1917 September 21-30 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - 1917 October 1-10 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 1917 October 11-20 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - 1917 October 21-31 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - 1917 November 1-10 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - 1917 November 11-20 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 1917 November 20-30 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - 1917 December 1-10 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - 1917 December 11-20 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - 1917 December 21-31 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - 1916 December 1-10 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 1916 December 1-10 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 1916 December 11-20 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - 1916 December 11-20 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - 1916 December 21-31 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - 1916 December 21-23 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - 1916 December 24-31 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - 1917 January 1-10 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - 1917 January 1-10 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 1917 January 11-20 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - 1917 January 11-20 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - 1917 January 21-31 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - 1917 January 21-31 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - SM Realty., 1917 January 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - 1917 February 1-10 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 1917 February 1-10 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - 1917 February 11-16 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - 1917 February 17-20 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - 1917 February 21-24 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - 1917 February 25-28 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - 1917 March 1-5 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 1917 March 6-10 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 1915 August 21-31 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 1915 September 1-4 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - 1915 September 5-10 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - 1915 September 11-20 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 1915 September 21-25 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1915 September 26-30 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - 1915 October 1-10 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - 1915 October 11-20 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - 1915 October 21-31 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 1915 November 1-10 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - 1915 November 11-20 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 1915 November 21-26 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - 1915 November 27-30 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 1915 December 1-5 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - 1915 December 6-10 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - 1915 December 11-15 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - 1915 December 16-20 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 1915 December 21-31 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 1915 December 21-31 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 1916 January 1-10 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 1916 January 1-10 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 1916 January 11-20 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 1916 January 21-31 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 1916 January 21-31 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 1916 January 11-20 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 1916 May 1-10 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 1916 May 1-10 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 1916 May 11-20 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - 1916 May 11-20 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 1916 May 21-31 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 1916 May 21-31 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 1916 July 1-10 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - 1916 July 11-14 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - 1916 July 15-20 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - 1916 July 21-31 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - 1916 July 21-31 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - 1916 August 1-10 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 1916 August 1-10 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - 1918-1919, [1 of 8 folders.] (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 1918-1919, [2 of 8 folders.] (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 1918-1919, [3 of 8 folders.] (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - 1918-1919, [4 of 8 folders.] (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - 1918-1919, [5 of 8 folders.] (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - 1918-1919, [6 of 8 folders.] (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 1918-1919, [7 of 8 folders.] (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 1918-1919, [8 of 8 folders.] (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - 1919, [1 of 14 folders.] (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - 1919, [2 of 14 folders.] (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - 1919, [3 of 14 folders.] (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - 1919, [4 of 14 folders.] (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - 1919, [5 of 14 folders.] (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - 1919, [6 of 14 folders.] (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - 1919, [7 of 14 folders.] (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 1919, [8 of 14 folders.] (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - 1919, [9 of 14 folders.] (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - 1919, [10 of 14 folders.] (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 1919, [11 of 14 folders.] (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - 1919, [12 of 14 folders.] (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - 1919, [13 of 14 folders.] (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - 1919, [14 of 14 folders.] (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - 1920, [1 of 17 folders.] (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - 1920, [2 of 17 folders.] (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - 1920, [3 of 17 folders.] (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - 1920, [4 of 17 folders.] (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - 1920, [5 of 17 folders.] (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - 1920, [6 of 17 folders.] (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - 1920, [7 of 17 folders.] (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - 1920, [8 of 17 folders.] (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - 1920, [9 of 17 folders.] (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - 1920, [10 of 17 folders.] (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - 1920, [11 of 17 folders.] (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 1920, [12 of 17 folders.] (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - 1920, [13 of 17 folders.] (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - 1920, [14 of 17 folders.] (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - 1920, [15 of 17 folders.] (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - 1920, [16 of 17 folders.] (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - 1920, [17 of 17 folders.] (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - 1921, [1 of 9 folders.] (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - 1921, [2 of 9 folders.] (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - 1921, [3 of 9 folders.] (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - 1921, [4 of 9 folders.] (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - 1921, [5 of 9 folders.] (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - 1921, [6 of 9 folders.] (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - 1921, [7 of 9 folders.] (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - 1921, [8 of 9 folders.] (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - 1921, [9 of 9 folders.] (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - 1922, [1 of 8 folders.] (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - 1922, [2 of 8 folders.] (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - 1922, [3 of 8 folders.] (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - 1922, [4 of 8 folders.] (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - 1922, [5 of 8 folders.] (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - 1922, [6 of 8 folders.] (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - 1922, [7 of 8 folders.] (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - 1922, [8 of 8 folders.] (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 1923, [1 of 6 folders.] (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - 1923, [2 of 6 folders.] (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - 1923, [3 of 6 folders.] (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - 1923, [4 of 6 folders.] (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - 1923, [5 of 6 folders.] (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - 1923, [6 of 6 folders.] (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - 1924-1926, [1 of 2 folders.] (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - 1924-1926, [2 of 2 folders.] (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - 1902-1905 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - 1906 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - 1907 January-April (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - 1907 May-August (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - 1907 September-1908 January (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - 1908 February-June (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - 1908 July-October (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - 1908 November-December (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - 1910 January-March (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - 1910 April-May (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 1910 June-July (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - 1910 August-October (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 1911 February-May (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 1911 June-November (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - 1911 December (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - 1912 January-May (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - 1912 June-October (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - 1918, [1 of 17 folders.] (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - 1918, [2 of 17 folders.] (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - 1918, [3 of 17 folders.] (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - 1918, [4 of 17 folders.] (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - 1918, [5 of 17 folders.] (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - 1918, [6 of 17 folders.] (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - 1918, [7 of 17 folders.] (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - 1918, [8 of 17 folders.] (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - 1918, [9 of 17 folders.] (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - 1918, [10 of 17 folders.] (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - 1918, [11 of 17 folders.] (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - 1918, [12 of 17 folders.] (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - 1918, [13 of 17 folders.] (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - 1918, [14 of 17 folders.] (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - 1918, [15 of 17 folders.] (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - 1918, [16 of 17 folders.] (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - 1918, [17 of 17 folders.] (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - 1916 February 1-10 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - 1916 February 1-10 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - 1916 February 11-20 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - 1916 February 11-20 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - 1916 February 21-29 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 1916 February 21-25 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - 1916 February 26-29 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - 1916 November 1-10 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - 1916 November 1-10 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - 1916 November 11-14 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - 1916 November 15-20 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - 1916 November 21-30 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - 1916 November 21-30 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Oakland Station., 1916 June-November (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - 1910 October-November (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - 1910 December (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - 1911 January (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - 1911 February (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - 1911 March (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - 1917 March 11-20 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - 1917 March 11-20 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - 1917 March 21-31 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - 1917 March 21-31 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - 1917 April 1-5 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - 1917 April 6-10 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - 1911 August (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - 1911 September (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - 1911 October 1-15 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - 1911 October 16-31 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - 1911 November 1-15 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - 1911 November 16-30 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 1916 April 1-10 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - 1916 April 1-10 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - 1916 April 11-20 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - 1916 April 11-20 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - 1916 April 21-25 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - 1916 April 26-30 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - 1917 June 1-10 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - 1917 June 11-15 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - 1917 June 16-20 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - 1917 June 21-25 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - 1917 June 26-30 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - 1906-1923, [1 of 2 folders.] (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - 1906-1923, [2 of 2 folders.] (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - 1912-1914 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - 1912-1917 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 1913-1917 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - 1914-1917 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - [undated] (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - [undated] (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - [undated] (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - [undated] (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - [undated] (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - 1911-1912 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - 1907-1912, [1 of 2 folders.] (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - 1907-1912, [2 of 2 folders.] (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - 1906-1914 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - 1910-1916 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - 1920-1921 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - 1916-1918 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - 1907-1918 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - 1917 (Box 90)
  - 1916-1917 (Box 91)
  - 1916-1917, [1 of 3 folders.] (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - 1916-1917, [2 of 3 folders.] (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - 1916-1917, [3 of 3 folders.] (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - 1907-1914 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Including correspondence and reports from the Federal Trade Commission and the U.S. Geological Survey., 1915-1917 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - 1907-1910 (Box 95)
  - 1917-1918 (Box 97)
  - 1912-1915 (Box 98)
  - 1910-1920 (Box 99)
  - 1918-1919 (Box 118)
- Financial Records and Reports
  - 1912 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1913 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 1914 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 1915 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 1924-1926, [1 of 5 folders.] (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - 1924-1926, [2 of 5 folders.] (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - 1924-1926, [3 of 5 folders.] (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 1924-1926, [4 of 5 folders.] (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - 1920-1923, [1 of 9 folders.] (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - 1920-1923, [2 of 9 folders.] (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - 1920-1923, [3 of 9 folders.] (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - 1920-1923, [4 of 9 folders.] (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - 1920-1923, [5 of 9 folders.] (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - 1920-1923, [6 of 9 folders.] (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - 1920-1923, [7 of 9 folders.] (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - 1920-1923, [8 of 9 folders.] (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - 1924-1926, [5 of 5 folders.] (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - 1923 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - 1920-1923, [9 of 9 folders.] (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - 1915-1919 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - 1911 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - 1914-1920 (Box 79)
  - 1902-1920 (Box 80)
  - 1910-1914 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Stock certificates., 1907-1910 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Voucher checks., 1910; [1 of 5 folders.] (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Voucher checks., 1910; [2 of 5 folders.] (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Voucher checks., 1910; [3 of 5 folders.] (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Voucher checks., 1910; [4 of 5 folders.] (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Voucher checks., 1910; [5 of 5 folders.] (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - 1910-1911, [1 of 4 folders.] (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - 1910-1911, [2 of 4 folders.] (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - 1910-1911, [3 of 4 folders.] (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - 1910-1911, [4 of 4 folders.] (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - 1901-1920 (Box 84)
  - 1917 (Box 86)
  - Ledgers., [undated]; [5 items] (Box 87)
  - 1917 (Box 90)
  - Ledgers., 1917; [5 items] (Box 96)
  - 1910-1920 (Box 99)
  - Ledgers., 1903-1919; [6 items] (Box 100)
  - Ledgers, including accounts of Carpinteria Oil Company and Vesper Mining Company., 1907-1916; [4 items] (Box 101)
  - Stock certificates of Vesper Mining Company., 1910 (Box 102)
  - undated, [oversized] (Box 103)
  - Payroll. Payroll. 1910-1911, [oversized] (Box 104)
  - Loose ledger pages and balance sheets., 1912-1916; [oversized] (Box 105)
  - Ledger and payroll. Payroll., 1910-1919; [oversized] (Box 106)
  - Loose ledger pages., 1914; [oversized] (Box 107)
  - Stock certificates., 1918-1920; [oversized] (Box 115)
  - 1916-1919 (Box 118)
  - 1909-1919 (Box 119)
- Inventories and Tour Reports
  - [undated] (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - 1914-1920 (Box 79)
  - 1902-1920 (Box 80)
  - 1901-1920 (Box 84)
  - Driller's Tour Reports., [undated]; [9 items] (Box 88)
  - 1903-1917 (Box 89)
  - 1916, [1 of 2 folders.] (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - 1916, [2 of 2 folders.] (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - 1917, [1 of 4 folders.] (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - 1917, [2 of 4 folders.] (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - 1917, [3 of 4 folders.] (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - 1917, [4 of 4 folders.] (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Including Graciosa Oil Wells reports., 1906-1917; [2 items] (Box 101)
  - 1914-1917, [2 items] (Box 102)
  - 1917, [oversized] (Box 103)
  - Driller's tour report book., 1911; [oversized] (Box 107)
  - 1910-1914, [oversized. 1 item.] (Box 117)
- Legal Documents
  - 1914-1920 (Box 79)
  - 1902-1920 (Box 80)
  - Including articles of incorporation., 1901-1920 (Box 84)